Maggie Gibson Graphic & Web Designer

Creative and motivated graphic designer and web designer based out of NYC and TX. I create design systems and content that are functional, organized, and custom-tailored to the needs of the project. I combine my design knowledge and skills with my passion for coding to create immersive and responsive web design and user experiences.

maggiegibson.design 214-604-3728 maggieegibson7@gmail.com



Work Experience

It's Gigi LLC, Graphic Designer

VEMBER 2022 - PRESENT, NEW YORK, NY

Designed social media and website content with custom designed and illustrated assets, created and evolved consistent brand identities for different projects for multiple platforms, and utilized design solutions for information sharing across platforms and presentations.

Digiblox.io, Creative Direction Intern

JUNE 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022, DALLAS, TX

Created new and innovative e-commerce websites, developed social media outreach marketing materials and strategies, and oversaw creative direction of projects.

Hazy Mae, Graphic Design Intern

FEBRUARY 2022 - JUNE 2022, NEW YORK, NY

Designed business merchandise from business cards to wallpaper, creating digital marketing content, including motion graphics and text layouts, for social media, and organized a design system for inventory and business endeavors.

Dallas Museum of Art, Teen Advisory Council Member AUGUST 2017 - JUNE 2019, DALLAS, TX

Organized and brainstormed community art events, created marketing and branding for events to promote engagement, and collaborated with fellow council members and assisted in delegating responsibilities.

Education

Parsons School of Design

AUGUST 2019 - MAY 2023 BFA — Communication Design



Toolkit

InDesign

Illustrator

Photoshop

AfterEffects

Procreate

Adobe Express

Javascript

HTML

CSS

p5.js

Figma

Processing.py

Skills

Creative Coding User Interaction and Experience Branding and Identity Web Design and Development **Digital Illustration** Motion Design and Motion Graphics **Digital Layout Data Visualization**